{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338068498","data":{"timestamp":" 947338068497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" amelala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338069580","data":{"timestamp":" 947338069579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" amelala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338074929","data":{"timestamp":" 947338074929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sherehe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" SHEREHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338075993","data":{"timestamp":" 947338075992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sherehe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" SHEREHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338084478","data":{"timestamp":" 947338084477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kungoja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGOJA"," userResponse":" KUNGOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338085548","data":{"timestamp":" 947338085548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kungoja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGOJA"," userResponse":" KUNGOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338089601","data":{"timestamp":" 947338089600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makubwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" START_MAKUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338096963","data":{"timestamp":" 947338096962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makubwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338098043","data":{"timestamp":" 947338098042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makubwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338109942","data":{"timestamp":" 947338109942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umeiona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEIONA"," userResponse":" UMEIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338111004","data":{"timestamp":" 947338111004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" umeiona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEIONA"," userResponse":" UMEIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338117590","data":{"timestamp":" 947338117590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338118668","data":{"timestamp":" 947338118667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alikuwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338122367","data":{"timestamp":" 947338122366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uchungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" UCHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338123419","data":{"timestamp":" 947338123418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uchungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHUNGU"," userResponse":" UCHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338127313","data":{"timestamp":" 947338127312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hutoboa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUTOBOA"," userResponse":" HUTOBOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338128378","data":{"timestamp":" 947338128377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hutoboa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUTOBOA"," userResponse":" HUTOBOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338134657","data":{"timestamp":" 947338134656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikipiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIPIGA"," userResponse":" IKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338135718","data":{"timestamp":" 947338135718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikipiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIPIGA"," userResponse":" IKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338141035","data":{"timestamp":" 947338141035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" magunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338142100","data":{"timestamp":" 947338142099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" magunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338145981","data":{"timestamp":" 947338145980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" magunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338146125","data":{"timestamp":" 947338146125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 8e23ee27-cfef-4801-9c1e-2470df28b4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__HF.wrd.len-7.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" magunia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338288066","data":{"timestamp":" 947338288065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338288952","data":{"timestamp":" 947338288951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338289600","data":{"timestamp":" 947338289599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338290473","data":{"timestamp":" 947338290472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338290629","data":{"timestamp":" 947338290628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338291166","data":{"timestamp":" 947338291166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338303599","data":{"timestamp":" 947338303598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338308883","data":{"timestamp":" 947338308882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338310878","data":{"timestamp":" 947338310878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338312464","data":{"timestamp":" 947338312463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338312752","data":{"timestamp":" 947338312752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338323091","data":{"timestamp":" 947338323091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa rafiki mkubwa wa Kima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338325495","data":{"timestamp":" 947338325494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walishiriki mambo mengi pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIRIKI"," userResponse":" WALISHIRIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338325961","data":{"timestamp":" 947338325960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walishiriki mambo mengi pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338326838","data":{"timestamp":" 947338326838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walishiriki mambo mengi pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338327585","data":{"timestamp":" 947338327584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walishiriki mambo mengi pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338329717","data":{"timestamp":" 947338329716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walishiriki mambo mengi pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIRIKI"," userResponse":" START_WALISHIRIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338331627","data":{"timestamp":" 947338331627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walishiriki mambo mengi pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIRIKI"," userResponse":" START_WALISHIRIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338333666","data":{"timestamp":" 947338333666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walishiriki mambo mengi pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIRIKI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338334935","data":{"timestamp":" 947338334934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walishiriki mambo mengi pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338336536","data":{"timestamp":" 947338336536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walishiriki mambo mengi pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338338142","data":{"timestamp":" 947338338141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walishiriki mambo mengi pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338340538","data":{"timestamp":" 947338340537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338341168","data":{"timestamp":" 947338341167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338342084","data":{"timestamp":" 947338342083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338343046","data":{"timestamp":" 947338343046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338344284","data":{"timestamp":" 947338344283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338344821","data":{"timestamp":" 947338344820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338345945","data":{"timestamp":" 947338345945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATEMBEZI"," userResponse":" MATEMBEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338347175","data":{"timestamp":" 947338347174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATAFUTE"," userResponse":" TUKATAFUTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338347875","data":{"timestamp":" 947338347874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338349840","data":{"timestamp":" 947338349840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338351248","data":{"timestamp":" 947338351247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338352727","data":{"timestamp":" 947338352727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338354474","data":{"timestamp":" 947338354473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338356510","data":{"timestamp":" 947338356510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338358529","data":{"timestamp":" 947338358529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338359833","data":{"timestamp":" 947338359833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338360562","data":{"timestamp":" 947338360562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATEMBEZI"," userResponse":" START_MATEMBEZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338361710","data":{"timestamp":" 947338361710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATEMBEZI"," userResponse":" MATEMBEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338363503","data":{"timestamp":" 947338363503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATAFUTE"," userResponse":" TUKATAFUTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338365123","data":{"timestamp":" 947338365123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Sungura alisema Hebu twende matembezi tukatafute chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338366843","data":{"timestamp":" 947338366843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338367932","data":{"timestamp":" 947338367931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUBALI"," userResponse":" ALIKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338368367","data":{"timestamp":" 947338368367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338369145","data":{"timestamp":" 947338369144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338370494","data":{"timestamp":" 947338370493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIYOMSUBIRI"," userResponse":" YALIYOMSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338372399","data":{"timestamp":" 947338372399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338373795","data":{"timestamp":" 947338373795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUBALI"," userResponse":" START_ALIKUBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338377671","data":{"timestamp":" 947338377670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338382848","data":{"timestamp":" 947338382848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338387793","data":{"timestamp":" 947338387793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338391133","data":{"timestamp":" 947338391132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338392700","data":{"timestamp":" 947338392699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YALIYOMSUBIRI"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338394838","data":{"timestamp":" 947338394837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YALIYOMSUBIRI"," userResponse":" START_YALIYOMSUBIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338397145","data":{"timestamp":" 947338397144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima alikubali bila kujua yaliyomsubiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIYOMSUBIRI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338399819","data":{"timestamp":" 947338399819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338400464","data":{"timestamp":" 947338400464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338400964","data":{"timestamp":" 947338400964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338401230","data":{"timestamp":" 947338401229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338401999","data":{"timestamp":" 947338401998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338402577","data":{"timestamp":" 947338402576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338403316","data":{"timestamp":" 947338403315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338403824","data":{"timestamp":" 947338403824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338404882","data":{"timestamp":" 947338404881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338406863","data":{"timestamp":" 947338406862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338408171","data":{"timestamp":" 947338408171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338409754","data":{"timestamp":" 947338409754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338411073","data":{"timestamp":" 947338411073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338412805","data":{"timestamp":" 947338412805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338414948","data":{"timestamp":" 947338414947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338416402","data":{"timestamp":" 947338416402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338418058","data":{"timestamp":" 947338418057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338418354","data":{"timestamp":" 947338418354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338429639","data":{"timestamp":" 947338429639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338430768","data":{"timestamp":" 947338430767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" START_MAHINDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338432939","data":{"timestamp":" 947338432938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda katika shamba la wenyewe na kuanza kula mahindi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338434952","data":{"timestamp":" 947338434951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338435809","data":{"timestamp":" 947338435809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338436064","data":{"timestamp":" 947338436063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338436805","data":{"timestamp":" 947338436804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAMA"," userResponse":" NJAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338437330","data":{"timestamp":" 947338437329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338438350","data":{"timestamp":" 947338438349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTENDEA"," userResponse":" KUMTENDEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338438989","data":{"timestamp":" 947338438988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338439555","data":{"timestamp":" 947338439554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UOVU"," userResponse":" UOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338445842","data":{"timestamp":" 947338445842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338449033","data":{"timestamp":" 947338449033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338463624","data":{"timestamp":" 947338463624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338465406","data":{"timestamp":" 947338465406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338465423","data":{"timestamp":" 947338465422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAMA"," userResponse":" NJAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338466480","data":{"timestamp":" 947338466480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338466981","data":{"timestamp":" 947338466980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTENDEA"," userResponse":" NJAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338468849","data":{"timestamp":" 947338468849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTENDEA"," userResponse":" KUMTENDEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338470265","data":{"timestamp":" 947338470264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" START_NJAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338474006","data":{"timestamp":" 947338474006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338478229","data":{"timestamp":" 947338478228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UOVU"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338480821","data":{"timestamp":" 947338480821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UOVU"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338482402","data":{"timestamp":" 947338482402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikuwa na njama ya kumtendea Kima uovu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UOVU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338484900","data":{"timestamp":" 947338484900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338486220","data":{"timestamp":" 947338486219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338486756","data":{"timestamp":" 947338486756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338487530","data":{"timestamp":" 947338487530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIVU"," userResponse":" WIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338488270","data":{"timestamp":" 947338488269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338488749","data":{"timestamp":" 947338488748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338489035","data":{"timestamp":" 947338489035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338489730","data":{"timestamp":" 947338489729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338490481","data":{"timestamp":" 947338490481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338492641","data":{"timestamp":" 947338492641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" START_SUNGURA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338494296","data":{"timestamp":" 947338494295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" START_SUNGURA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338496065","data":{"timestamp":" 947338496064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338508142","data":{"timestamp":" 947338508141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338509010","data":{"timestamp":" 947338509010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338510198","data":{"timestamp":" 947338510197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WIVU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338512050","data":{"timestamp":" 947338512049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIVU"," userResponse":" WIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338513128","data":{"timestamp":" 947338513128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338525505","data":{"timestamp":" 947338525505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338527653","data":{"timestamp":" 947338527653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338530606","data":{"timestamp":" 947338530606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338532125","data":{"timestamp":" 947338532124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" START_MREFU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338535199","data":{"timestamp":" 947338535199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alimwonea Kima wivu kwa kuwa na mkia mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338537247","data":{"timestamp":" 947338537246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338538458","data":{"timestamp":" 947338538457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" AMEZUNGUMZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338538726","data":{"timestamp":" 947338538724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338539112","data":{"timestamp":" 947338539112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338539795","data":{"timestamp":" 947338539794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338541880","data":{"timestamp":" 947338541880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338543113","data":{"timestamp":" 947338543112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" START_AMEZUNGUMZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338551956","data":{"timestamp":" 947338551955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338555126","data":{"timestamp":" 947338555126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338557382","data":{"timestamp":" 947338557382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338558984","data":{"timestamp":" 947338558984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338560322","data":{"timestamp":" 947338560321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" START_SHAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338562207","data":{"timestamp":" 947338562207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amezungumza na wenye shamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338563924","data":{"timestamp":" 947338563924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338565042","data":{"timestamp":" 947338565040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUJA"," userResponse":" ATAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338565572","data":{"timestamp":" 947338565571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338566293","data":{"timestamp":" 947338566292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338567073","data":{"timestamp":" 947338567072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" YENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338567458","data":{"timestamp":" 947338567458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338569347","data":{"timestamp":" 947338569347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338570967","data":{"timestamp":" 947338570966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUJA"," userResponse":" ATAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338573572","data":{"timestamp":" 947338573572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338575305","data":{"timestamp":" 947338575304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338576487","data":{"timestamp":" 947338576487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338576893","data":{"timestamp":" 947338576893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" YENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338577889","data":{"timestamp":" 947338577888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima atakuja kula mahindi yenu leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338579692","data":{"timestamp":" 947338579691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfunze adabu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUNZE"," userResponse":" MFUNZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338581202","data":{"timestamp":" 947338581202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfunze adabu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADABU"," userResponse":" ADABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338583451","data":{"timestamp":" 947338583450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfunze adabu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUNZE"," userResponse":" MFUNZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338584896","data":{"timestamp":" 947338584895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfunze adabu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ADABU"," userResponse":" START_ADABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338586815","data":{"timestamp":" 947338586814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mfunze adabu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADABU"," userResponse":" ADABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338589704","data":{"timestamp":" 947338589703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338590364","data":{"timestamp":" 947338590364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKILA"," userResponse":" WAKILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338591433","data":{"timestamp":" 947338591432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338592543","data":{"timestamp":" 947338592543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338593969","data":{"timestamp":" 947338593967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338594517","data":{"timestamp":" 947338594516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338595182","data":{"timestamp":" 947338595181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPIGA"," userResponse":" KUPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338595937","data":{"timestamp":" 947338595937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338596911","data":{"timestamp":" 947338596911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISEMA"," userResponse":" AKISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338598404","data":{"timestamp":" 947338598404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWIZI"," userResponse":" MWIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338601290","data":{"timestamp":" 947338601290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338603216","data":{"timestamp":" 947338603216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338605106","data":{"timestamp":" 947338605105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338607627","data":{"timestamp":" 947338607627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338609088","data":{"timestamp":" 947338609088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338612530","data":{"timestamp":" 947338612530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" START_SUNGURA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338614195","data":{"timestamp":" 947338614195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338616066","data":{"timestamp":" 947338616066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338617699","data":{"timestamp":" 947338617698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338618404","data":{"timestamp":" 947338618404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPIGA"," userResponse":" KUPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338619773","data":{"timestamp":" 947338619773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338621925","data":{"timestamp":" 947338621925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKISEMA"," userResponse":" MWIZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338624931","data":{"timestamp":" 947338624930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338632745","data":{"timestamp":" 947338632744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa wakila mahindi Sungura alijificha na kupiga kelele akisema Mwizi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338634849","data":{"timestamp":" 947338634849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mahindi yenu yanaliwa yote!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338635245","data":{"timestamp":" 947338635245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mahindi yenu yanaliwa yote!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" YENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338636093","data":{"timestamp":" 947338636092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mahindi yenu yanaliwa yote!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANALIWA"," userResponse":" YANALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338636992","data":{"timestamp":" 947338636991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mahindi yenu yanaliwa yote!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338641278","data":{"timestamp":" 947338641278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mahindi yenu yanaliwa yote!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338642881","data":{"timestamp":" 947338642881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mahindi yenu yanaliwa yote!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENU"," userResponse":" YENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338644221","data":{"timestamp":" 947338644220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mahindi yenu yanaliwa yote!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANALIWA"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338646591","data":{"timestamp":" 947338646590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mahindi yenu yanaliwa yote!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YANALIWA"," userResponse":" AKISEMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338648369","data":{"timestamp":" 947338648369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mahindi yenu yanaliwa yote!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANALIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338649776","data":{"timestamp":" 947338649775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mahindi yenu yanaliwa yote!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338651532","data":{"timestamp":" 947338651531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338652583","data":{"timestamp":" 947338652583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOROKA"," userResponse":" AKATOROKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338652789","data":{"timestamp":" 947338652788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338653297","data":{"timestamp":" 947338653296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338653845","data":{"timestamp":" 947338653844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338655669","data":{"timestamp":" 947338655669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338656970","data":{"timestamp":" 947338656970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOROKA"," userResponse":" START_AKATOROKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338658806","data":{"timestamp":" 947338658806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOROKA"," userResponse":" START_AKATOROKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338660840","data":{"timestamp":" 947338660840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOROKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338663385","data":{"timestamp":" 947338663385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338664709","data":{"timestamp":" 947338664708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" START_KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338668114","data":{"timestamp":" 947338668113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" START_KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338669684","data":{"timestamp":" 947338669684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338671082","data":{"timestamp":" 947338671082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338673045","data":{"timestamp":" 947338673045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akatoroka na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338674688","data":{"timestamp":" 947338674687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima hakujua lililokuwa likiendelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338675459","data":{"timestamp":" 947338675458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima hakujua lililokuwa likiendelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUJUA"," userResponse":" HAKUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338676556","data":{"timestamp":" 947338676555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima hakujua lililokuwa likiendelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338677696","data":{"timestamp":" 947338677695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima hakujua lililokuwa likiendelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIENDELEA"," userResponse":" LIKIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338679868","data":{"timestamp":" 947338679868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima hakujua lililokuwa likiendelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338681277","data":{"timestamp":" 947338681277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima hakujua lililokuwa likiendelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUJUA"," userResponse":" HAKUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338683365","data":{"timestamp":" 947338683365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima hakujua lililokuwa likiendelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LILILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338684678","data":{"timestamp":" 947338684677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima hakujua lililokuwa likiendelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIENDELEA"," userResponse":" START_LIKIENDELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338687051","data":{"timestamp":" 947338687051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima hakujua lililokuwa likiendelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIENDELEA"," userResponse":" START_LIKIENDELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338688914","data":{"timestamp":" 947338688914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima hakujua lililokuwa likiendelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIENDELEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338692024","data":{"timestamp":" 947338692024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" WALIMFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338692201","data":{"timestamp":" 947338692201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIPIGA"," userResponse":" WAKIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338692716","data":{"timestamp":" 947338692716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338692868","data":{"timestamp":" 947338692868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338697312","data":{"timestamp":" 947338697310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" START_WALIMFUATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338700539","data":{"timestamp":" 947338700538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" START_WALIMFUATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338702656","data":{"timestamp":" 947338702656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338703157","data":{"timestamp":" 947338703157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIPIGA"," userResponse":" START_WAKIPIGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338727830","data":{"timestamp":" 947338727830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338738396","data":{"timestamp":" 947338738396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338764440","data":{"timestamp":" 947338764440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimfuata wakipiga kelele Simama!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338766970","data":{"timestamp":" 947338766970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umetumalizia mahindi yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMETUMALIZIA"," userResponse":" UMETUMALIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338767700","data":{"timestamp":" 947338767699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umetumalizia mahindi yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338768152","data":{"timestamp":" 947338768151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umetumalizia mahindi yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338779739","data":{"timestamp":" 947338779739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umetumalizia mahindi yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMETUMALIZIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338784907","data":{"timestamp":" 947338784907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umetumalizia mahindi yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338785021","data":{"timestamp":" 947338785020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umetumalizia mahindi yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338788163","data":{"timestamp":" 947338788162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimshika na kuanza kumpiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMSHIKA"," userResponse":" WALIMSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338788367","data":{"timestamp":" 947338788367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimshika na kuanza kumpiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338788979","data":{"timestamp":" 947338788979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimshika na kuanza kumpiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338790153","data":{"timestamp":" 947338790153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimshika na kuanza kumpiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPIGA"," userResponse":" KUMPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338790286","data":{"timestamp":" 947338790286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Walimshika na kuanza kumpiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338790387","data":{"timestamp":" 947338790387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimshika na kuanza kumpiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPIGA"," userResponse":" KUMPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338812595","data":{"timestamp":" 947338812595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 619d9cf1-984b-45e2-931f-c2f4a2ca12f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Walimshika na kuanza kumpiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338855535","data":{"timestamp":" 947338855535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" Q"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338861924","data":{"timestamp":" 947338861924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338872625","data":{"timestamp":" 947338872625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338879537","data":{"timestamp":" 947338879537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338884368","data":{"timestamp":" 947338884368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338890298","data":{"timestamp":" 947338890297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338897280","data":{"timestamp":" 947338897280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338904957","data":{"timestamp":" 947338904957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338909546","data":{"timestamp":" 947338909546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338918787","data":{"timestamp":" 947338918787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338931244","data":{"timestamp":" 947338931243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338940365","data":{"timestamp":" 947338940365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338944208","data":{"timestamp":" 947338944207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akipiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338974714","data":{"timestamp":" 947338974714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338988528","data":{"timestamp":" 947338988528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947338997570","data":{"timestamp":" 947338997570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339014940","data":{"timestamp":" 947339014940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339020664","data":{"timestamp":" 947339020663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339032251","data":{"timestamp":" 947339032251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339038094","data":{"timestamp":" 947339038094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339043888","data":{"timestamp":" 947339043888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_maanake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339061790","data":{"timestamp":" 947339061790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339070152","data":{"timestamp":" 947339070152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339080548","data":{"timestamp":" 947339080548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339088248","data":{"timestamp":" 947339088248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339105908","data":{"timestamp":" 947339105907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339115909","data":{"timestamp":" 947339115909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339126483","data":{"timestamp":" 947339126483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339132748","data":{"timestamp":" 947339132748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339135464","data":{"timestamp":" 947339135463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339138433","data":{"timestamp":" 947339138433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339142820","data":{"timestamp":" 947339142820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339150898","data":{"timestamp":" 947339150898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339153997","data":{"timestamp":" 947339153997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuliita"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339175751","data":{"timestamp":" 947339175751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339182443","data":{"timestamp":" 947339182443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339186071","data":{"timestamp":" 947339186071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339189688","data":{"timestamp":" 947339189688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339193305","data":{"timestamp":" 947339193305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339197563","data":{"timestamp":" 947339197563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339200906","data":{"timestamp":" 947339200906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339204856","data":{"timestamp":" 947339204856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339211541","data":{"timestamp":" 947339211541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sherehe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339241634","data":{"timestamp":" 947339241634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339249120","data":{"timestamp":" 947339249119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339253308","data":{"timestamp":" 947339253308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339258168","data":{"timestamp":" 947339258168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339266455","data":{"timestamp":" 947339266454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339272896","data":{"timestamp":" 947339272895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339286702","data":{"timestamp":" 947339286702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339295273","data":{"timestamp":" 947339295272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339299055","data":{"timestamp":" 947339299055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339309762","data":{"timestamp":" 947339309762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kipekee"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339329967","data":{"timestamp":" 947339329967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339353567","data":{"timestamp":" 947339353567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339359006","data":{"timestamp":" 947339359005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339366450","data":{"timestamp":" 947339366449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339371334","data":{"timestamp":" 947339371334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339377996","data":{"timestamp":" 947339377996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339384705","data":{"timestamp":" 947339384705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339390245","data":{"timestamp":" 947339390245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339399715","data":{"timestamp":" 947339399715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339406935","data":{"timestamp":" 947339406935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339418534","data":{"timestamp":" 947339418534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339423204","data":{"timestamp":" 947339423204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339448829","data":{"timestamp":" 947339448829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339456630","data":{"timestamp":" 947339456630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339465934","data":{"timestamp":" 947339465934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339473773","data":{"timestamp":" 947339473773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339476607","data":{"timestamp":" 947339476606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339481865","data":{"timestamp":" 947339481865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339489407","data":{"timestamp":" 947339489407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339494077","data":{"timestamp":" 947339494077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339499941","data":{"timestamp":" 947339499940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339511694","data":{"timestamp":" 947339511694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339517900","data":{"timestamp":" 947339517900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_akitela"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339537020","data":{"timestamp":" 947339537020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339540747","data":{"timestamp":" 947339540747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339545152","data":{"timestamp":" 947339545152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339550435","data":{"timestamp":" 947339550434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339557767","data":{"timestamp":" 947339557767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339622893","data":{"timestamp":" 947339622893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339628743","data":{"timestamp":" 947339628743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339631841","data":{"timestamp":" 947339631841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339638787","data":{"timestamp":" 947339638787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339655759","data":{"timestamp":" 947339655759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339699733","data":{"timestamp":" 947339699733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alikata"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339725134","data":{"timestamp":" 947339725134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339732737","data":{"timestamp":" 947339732736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339747940","data":{"timestamp":" 947339747940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339754777","data":{"timestamp":" 947339754777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339774298","data":{"timestamp":" 947339774297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339786193","data":{"timestamp":" 947339786193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339794811","data":{"timestamp":" 947339794811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alisema"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339814589","data":{"timestamp":" 947339814588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339828276","data":{"timestamp":" 947339828276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339835952","data":{"timestamp":" 947339835952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339845598","data":{"timestamp":" 947339845598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339853157","data":{"timestamp":" 947339853157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339860178","data":{"timestamp":" 947339860178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339870400","data":{"timestamp":" 947339870399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339879063","data":{"timestamp":" 947339879063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339889244","data":{"timestamp":" 947339889243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339901353","data":{"timestamp":" 947339901353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-7.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339928533","data":{"timestamp":" 947339928531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" 9c229aa2-7c3e-49fd-ac52-f3f3fc8b6c34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-7.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_mawimbi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339969392","data":{"timestamp":" 947339969392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339976489","data":{"timestamp":" 947339976488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339979557","data":{"timestamp":" 947339979557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339986739","data":{"timestamp":" 947339986739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947339992889","data":{"timestamp":" 947339992889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340003127","data":{"timestamp":" 947340003127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340012506","data":{"timestamp":" 947340012506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340018737","data":{"timestamp":" 947340018737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340029231","data":{"timestamp":" 947340029231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340034365","data":{"timestamp":" 947340034365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340038822","data":{"timestamp":" 947340038822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340043890","data":{"timestamp":" 947340043890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mishale"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340069120","data":{"timestamp":" 947340069119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340078348","data":{"timestamp":" 947340078348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340090957","data":{"timestamp":" 947340090957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340099537","data":{"timestamp":" 947340099537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340108582","data":{"timestamp":" 947340108582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340114568","data":{"timestamp":" 947340114568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340125890","data":{"timestamp":" 947340125890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340132101","data":{"timestamp":" 947340132100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340138632","data":{"timestamp":" 947340138632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340148526","data":{"timestamp":" 947340148525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340162372","data":{"timestamp":" 947340162372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340177552","data":{"timestamp":" 947340177552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340192922","data":{"timestamp":" 947340192921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340206699","data":{"timestamp":" 947340206699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340220205","data":{"timestamp":" 947340220205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340226594","data":{"timestamp":" 947340226594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340239583","data":{"timestamp":" 947340239583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340252583","data":{"timestamp":" 947340252582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340259491","data":{"timestamp":" 947340259491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340268484","data":{"timestamp":" 947340268484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340279354","data":{"timestamp":" 947340279354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340282757","data":{"timestamp":" 947340282756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340298393","data":{"timestamp":" 947340298393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-7.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340313580","data":{"timestamp":" 947340313580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" ea1cd4f5-ba3b-4687-8fb6-62cf03fac74c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_lc.wrd.len-7.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_chungwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340334273","data":{"timestamp":" 947340334272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340335447","data":{"timestamp":" 947340335447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340336355","data":{"timestamp":" 947340336354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340337445","data":{"timestamp":" 947340337444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340338468","data":{"timestamp":" 947340338468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340339336","data":{"timestamp":" 947340339335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340340445","data":{"timestamp":" 947340340445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKILALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340341118","data":{"timestamp":" 947340341117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340342418","data":{"timestamp":" 947340342417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340346211","data":{"timestamp":" 947340346210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340347339","data":{"timestamp":" 947340347339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340349551","data":{"timestamp":" 947340349551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340351365","data":{"timestamp":" 947340351364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340353830","data":{"timestamp":" 947340353830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340355745","data":{"timestamp":" 947340355745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340357536","data":{"timestamp":" 947340357535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340359245","data":{"timestamp":" 947340359244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKILALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340360859","data":{"timestamp":" 947340360859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340362435","data":{"timestamp":" 947340362434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340365021","data":{"timestamp":" 947340365021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340366777","data":{"timestamp":" 947340366777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340368764","data":{"timestamp":" 947340368764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340368951","data":{"timestamp":" 947340368951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340369931","data":{"timestamp":" 947340369930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340371310","data":{"timestamp":" 947340371309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" ULITENGEZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340371458","data":{"timestamp":" 947340371458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340372617","data":{"timestamp":" 947340372616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340373284","data":{"timestamp":" 947340373284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340374385","data":{"timestamp":" 947340374384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340375180","data":{"timestamp":" 947340375179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340375302","data":{"timestamp":" 947340375301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340376002","data":{"timestamp":" 947340376002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" MTENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340379178","data":{"timestamp":" 947340379178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340380470","data":{"timestamp":" 947340380469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340382983","data":{"timestamp":" 947340382983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340384804","data":{"timestamp":" 947340384804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" START_ULITENGEZWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340387354","data":{"timestamp":" 947340387353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" ULITENGEZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340389034","data":{"timestamp":" 947340389034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340389124","data":{"timestamp":" 947340389124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" START_SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340391172","data":{"timestamp":" 947340391172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340393959","data":{"timestamp":" 947340393959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340395584","data":{"timestamp":" 947340395583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340396742","data":{"timestamp":" 947340396741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340397974","data":{"timestamp":" 947340397974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340399095","data":{"timestamp":" 947340399095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" START_MTENDE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340401249","data":{"timestamp":" 947340401249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" MTENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340403649","data":{"timestamp":" 947340403646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340404527","data":{"timestamp":" 947340404526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340404767","data":{"timestamp":" 947340404766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340405388","data":{"timestamp":" 947340405388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340405505","data":{"timestamp":" 947340405504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340406514","data":{"timestamp":" 947340406513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340407422","data":{"timestamp":" 947340407421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340408122","data":{"timestamp":" 947340408122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340409403","data":{"timestamp":" 947340409401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" CHANIKIWITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340411669","data":{"timestamp":" 947340411669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340413543","data":{"timestamp":" 947340413542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340418716","data":{"timestamp":" 947340418716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340422921","data":{"timestamp":" 947340422921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340424363","data":{"timestamp":" 947340424362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340426375","data":{"timestamp":" 947340426375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340434098","data":{"timestamp":" 947340434097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340435534","data":{"timestamp":" 947340435533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340439677","data":{"timestamp":" 947340439677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340441076","data":{"timestamp":" 947340441075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340445048","data":{"timestamp":" 947340445048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340445131","data":{"timestamp":" 947340445131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" CHANIKIWITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340447216","data":{"timestamp":" 947340447215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340448264","data":{"timestamp":" 947340448262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340448469","data":{"timestamp":" 947340448469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340449191","data":{"timestamp":" 947340449188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKEKA"," userResponse":" MIKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340450198","data":{"timestamp":" 947340450198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGINE"," userResponse":" MINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340451198","data":{"timestamp":" 947340451198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340451948","data":{"timestamp":" 947340451947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340452550","data":{"timestamp":" 947340452549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340453411","data":{"timestamp":" 947340453411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340453924","data":{"timestamp":" 947340453923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340454778","data":{"timestamp":" 947340454777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340459628","data":{"timestamp":" 947340459627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340462824","data":{"timestamp":" 947340462823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340467789","data":{"timestamp":" 947340467789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340469381","data":{"timestamp":" 947340469381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MIKEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340470307","data":{"timestamp":" 947340470306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340471812","data":{"timestamp":" 947340471812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKEKA"," userResponse":" MIKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340473585","data":{"timestamp":" 947340473585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGINE"," userResponse":" MINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340476013","data":{"timestamp":" 947340476013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340477788","data":{"timestamp":" 947340477787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340479985","data":{"timestamp":" 947340479985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340481897","data":{"timestamp":" 947340481897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340483000","data":{"timestamp":" 947340483000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340484831","data":{"timestamp":" 947340484830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340487720","data":{"timestamp":" 947340487719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340488414","data":{"timestamp":" 947340488414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340489215","data":{"timestamp":" 947340489214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340490367","data":{"timestamp":" 947340490366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340491032","data":{"timestamp":" 947340491031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340491694","data":{"timestamp":" 947340491693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340492388","data":{"timestamp":" 947340492388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340493302","data":{"timestamp":" 947340493302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340493553","data":{"timestamp":" 947340493553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340493658","data":{"timestamp":" 947340493658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947340513776","data":{"timestamp":" 947340513776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_162727"," gameId":" c2897e8e-dc45-4d56-b11b-7ab15d91c25a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}